full stack developer

DENYS KRYCHEVSKYI

portfolio

CONTACTS -

+1 206 799 0080

krychevskyidenys@gmail.com 🗿

Seattle, WA 98112 🔘

Linkedin Profile in

GitHub Profile (7)

Facebook Profile (

EDUCATION —

Full-Stack Developer Certificate
Python Stack
Coding Dojo, Seattle 2020

Graphic Design Certificate Training Center "Specialist" MSTU. NE Bauman, Moscow, Russia, 2015

Bachelor's degree in Engineering Dnipro University of Technology Dnipro, Ukraine, 2003-2008

SKILLS -

Python, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS Django, Flask, Sass, BootStrap JQuery, AJAX MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL AWS EC2, Heroku Git, GitHub, Jira Software

DESIGN TOOLS —

Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Acrobat, Pit Stop Pro, Smart Stream Designer, Camera RAW

RECOGNITIONS —

Awarded Black Belt for Python Exam (top 5% of class)

INT Project were selected to be as promotion of the Coding Dojo school in social networks

Top performer recognition November 2018/Staples

HOBBY -

Basketball, Hiking Healthy food cooking

SUMMARY

Motivated and knowledge driven developer with background in Python, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, and building web applications from the ground up. 6+ years of experience in Graphic Design as well as expertise in print, packaging, marketing & advertising design. Advanced skills in Adobe Creative Suite, including Photoshop, Acrobat, Illustrator, and InDesign. Currently looking to join a team of passionate developers to create user-friendly web applications and products.

- TECHNICAL PROJECTS

INT

Social Media App | Python

Video | Live | Code

INT is a Social Media App, that allows users to create a personal profile, post photos, videos, music and text. Users can communicate with each other via chat, add comments, like/unlike posts or comments.

Fierce

Sportswear E-Commerce App | Python

Video | Live | Code

Fierce is an E-Commerce sportswear application. This app lets users view items, add items to a persistent cart, rate and review items, and ultimately buy items. Features a sleek and responsive user interface, that could rival many professional sites today. Collaborated with 3 man team in designing and implementing networking web app.

PROFI

Video | Live | Code

Job Search and Service Provider Web App | Python

Profi is Service Provider App, for people who looking for help with a job, and for people who provides services. Allows to create job in the pool or pick up job from the pool. User friendly dashboard, profile page, responsive design.

- EXPERIENCE

PRODUCTION ARTIST | Apr 2017 - Present

SGK Marketing & Advertising, Des Plaines, Illinois

Create high-quality artwork incorporating branding guidelines (photography, text, and legal requirements) into artwork layout per client's technical specifications; Ensure accurate, consistent, and timely completion of high quality basic to intermediate level artwork, effectively using industry standard software, tools, and print techniques.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | Nov 2017 – Apr 2020

Digi Copy & Print, Seattle, WA

Collaborated with design team to offer improvements and directions on client projects, contributing expertise during strategic brainstorming sessions that resulted in developing unique print materials (advertisement, brochures, and logo design) that met client needs

PRINT AND MARKETING SUPEVISOR | Nov 2017 - May 2019 Staples, Seattle, WA

Promoted from Associate to Supervisor within 1 year as a result of excellent management of multiple priorities while providing consultative interaction, producing top quality finished products, and establishing the opportunities to build business with customers.

Supervised the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the project.

Leverage sales and business expertise to train and mentor new associates in the department.